Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I’m Jay.
Chan’s ex-girlfriend.
What are you thinking?
Why are you so sure
that you can do anything to me?
Because I know that you still love me.
She set the no-kiss rule with you, right?
It means you and Chan
are not at the stage
where I have to be worried.
You can scold me or act coldly towards me.
I’m okay with it.
But don’t chase me away
like I were an animal.
I’m also a human.
Mom.
Let’s eat.
Today, we have chicken,
your favorite food.
I’ll feed you.
I don’t want to eat.
Please take a bite, Mom.
I told you I don’t want to eat.
Do you want to eat something else?
How about fruits?
Do you want to eat apples?
I’m not hungry.
Why do I need to repeat myself, Key?
You haven’t eaten anything
since yesterday.
Please eat something, Mom.
You are just my daughter.
Don’t order me around.
Just let me die.
No.
Mom, please eat something.
Please, Mom.
Get out.
But you haven’t eaten anything.
Why are you still here? Get out!
-Get out.
-No.
Get out!
No.
Get out. I told you to get out!
No, get out!
Mom.
Get out!
Get out. I told you to get out!
No, Mom.
No.
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
-Mom.
-Get out!
Get out!
-Pin.
Stop it.
-Stop it, Pin.
-Get out!
Get out!
Pin, what’s wrong with you?
She’s your daughter.
Why are you doing this to her?
Mom.
-Take her out of here.
-Key, are you alright? Walk slowly.
Let’s go.
How are you feeling?
Does it hurt a lot?
The wound on my head doesn’t hurt much.
But it really hurts here.
It’s okay.
If you feel hurt, just cry.
You have me.
I know that Mom didn’t mean to hurt me.
But it really hurts, Peach.
It hurts so much.
It’s okay.
Key, you are not alone.
You still have me.
Come here.
Cry as much as you want.
It will be alright.
It’s okay. You have me.
I’ll take the monitor off.
Mom.
Why don’t you stay at the hospital
for a night?
No, I’m fine.
But you passed out.
If Aunt Niam wasn’t there,
you would have fallen to the ground.
I’m just a little tired.
Key.
Are you alright?
Key, how did you know?
Peach called me.
She told me you passed out.
I’m okay.
I’ll feel better after getting some rest.
Are you sure? I’m worried about you.
I feel much better after seeing you.
(Hello.)
(Hello, Chan.)
(Do you hear me?)
Yes.
(What’s up?)
Tonight,
are you going to come to my condo?
I can’t.
(I’m tied up with some family matters.)
Is something wrong?
It’s nothing.
Are you worried about me?
I’m just asking.
That’s too bad.
I thought you were worried about me.
You are joking with me now.
So you are no longer mad at me, right?
I don’t know.
Please take care of Simba for me.
Simba will soon forget you.
You didn’t come to visit him at all.
Hello?
I’ll talk to you later.
Good night.
Yeah.
Your mommy is probably still mad at me.
What should I do to make up with her?
Thank you for coming home.
Sorry for suddenly asking you
to come home.
I should be the one who apologizes.
I barely come home to visit Big Mom.
I told Aunt Niam to prepare your room.
If you need anything,
you can always tell me.
Yes.
Thank you.
I’m glad
that you came home.
Yeah.
Key.
No one can hurt you now.
I promise.
I know.
Thank you, Peach.
Go.
Go take some rest.
Good night.
(I told you not to come back.
Why did you come back?)
(Why did you come back?)
(I was wrong.)
-(Why did you come back?)
-(I’m sorry.)
-(Didn’t I tell you not to come back?)
-(I was wrong.)
(I’m sorry.)
(Why did you come back?)
Key.
Key. Key.
It’s okay, Key.
Come here.
It’s okay. I’m right here.
It’s okay. It’s alright.
It’s okay.
Key.
It’s okay, Key.
There’s nothing to be scared of.
It’s nothing.
No one can hurt you now.
You have me.
It’s okay. Come here.
I’m right here.
You can’t sleep, Key?
Big Mom.
Why did you come out here?
You are still unwell.
I’m just like you.
I can’t sleep.
Today seems to be a good day.
You came back home to see me.
It’s also the first quarter moon tonight.
The first quarter moon?
Yes.
It said that it’s the strongest phase
of the lunar cycle.
The moon reaches a 90-degree angle
from the Sun and the Earth.
It’s the phase where,
if you have the determination, hope,
or will to do something, you can succeed.
You can conquer burdens
and overcome your fear.
No matter what happens,
you still have me, Peach, and your dad.
We always love you.
Thank you, Big Mom.
I’m sorry
for taking so long to come to visit you.
I love you, sweetie.
I love you too.
Why are you leaving so soon?
Can’t you stay a bit longer?
I have work to do.
I can’t skip it.
I also have an important errand to do.
Why don’t you quit your job
and come to work for our family business?
So you will have more free time.
No.
Asking me to quit singing is like
telling you to give up photographing.
Now, you know how to talk back to me.
Big Mom.
I’ll come to visit you more often.
Please take care of your health.
Yes.
Key, are you really not going
to have our chauffeur take you?
I can have someone
take your motorcycle to your condo.
I’m worried about you.
It’s okay, Big Mom.
Aunt Niam,
please take good care of Big Mom.
Sure.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take good care of her.
Great.
I’ve got to go.
I need to go to my condo to get changed.
Let’s have a meal together next time.
I want to see Dad too.
Yes.
I love you.
I’m leaving.
Bye.
Ride safely.
I will.
Let me help you.
It’s okay. I can do it myself.
Okay.
Thank you, Aunt Niam.
Ride safely.
Take care.
I’m leaving.
Bye.
I love you.
Love you too.
Please take care of her.
Ride safely.
She will come to visit you soon.
She’s really good on a motorcycle.
Don’t worry, Mom.
Chan.
Jay.
Have you eaten?
My restaurant launched
a soft opening today.
Can you go and taste the food?
You should ask someone else.
I have work to do.
You are the only one I want to ask.
Please.
Can’t you help me?
You can help me as the hotel’s owner.
And…
I have an important thing to tell you.
What is it?
Then come with me.
Please.
I’m begging you.
Please give me another chance.
Please.
Just one chance.
Let’s dine together, just the two of us.
Please.
Are you going out to eat?
Can I come with you?
I don’t remember inviting you.
Jay, you are opening a restaurant.
I’m sure you know that
turning away your customer
is unprofessional.
Okay.
Well said.
But I’m sorry.
I won’t let you come.
Jay, do you feel intimidated by me?
Fine.
You can come.
I’m asking you two. Can you stop fighting?
We are not fighting.
Right, Jay?
Yes.
We are not fighting.
You know a lot about food.
Can you taste it and give me feedback?
It tastes good.
But I think it’s a bit too heavy
for the first course.
You said it like
you know a lot about food.
I’m pretty good at it.
Stop it.
Both of you.
You said you have something to tell me.
What is it?
You can tell me here.
No.
I want to talk to you in private.
Then we have nothing to talk about.
I’m leaving.
I’m sorry
for leaving you to get married.
You’re sorry for leaving me
to get married?
Yes.
This is all I can say.
Can you forgive me?
Do you think that
your apology can fix everything?
Do you expect me to go back to you?
Jay.
Your apology is just an empty word.
It means nothing to me.
I know
that you were hurt when I left you.
But my hands were tied.
I had no choice.
You had no choice?
You had choices.
But you chose to leave me.
Whatever your reason was,
I’m not buying it.
Don’t be sad, Chan.
Are you no longer mad at me?
No. I’m not mad at you anymore.
Is it that easy?
Hey.
I’m just your sugar baby.
I can’t stay mad at you for long.
Otherwise, you might leave me.
I really don’t understand you.
Come on. Don’t be stressed.
So…
I can sleep at your place tonight,
can’t I?
Of course.
Are you going to leave your son with me?
You’re right.
I can’t leave our son.
Can I have four shots of vodka?
Serve them to me here.
Yes.
(Hello. Jay?)
(I called you several times.
Why didn’t you answer my calls?)
I’m busy.
What did you call me about?
(Where are you?)
It’s so loud there.
Just say what you want.
There’s a party at
Madam Ploy's this Saturday.
You need to go.
She hasn’t seen you for a while.
Why do I have to go?
We are not that close to her.
(I told you to go, you just go.
Stop asking questions.)
Can’t you do that for our family?
For our family? Again?
What I’ve done is not enough?
Jay, don’t raise your voice at me.
I’m doing all these things
for your future.
For me?
Or for yourself?
Morning, Simba.
Did your mommy wake up?
Where is she?
Do you want to watch the view?
Let’s watch the view.
Let’s watch it together.
I’ll put you down.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME. I MISS YOU SO MUCH.
Chan.
You’re up?
How did you know that I’m up?
I can sense it.
I know everything about you.
You are just guessing.
No.
I spent a lot of time with you.
Now, I know your every move.
I know what time you wake up.
Even without an alarm clock,
you wake up at the same time every day.
You sure know a lot.
Of course.
Because I’m your sugar baby.
Do you want to have your breakfast now?
Pepper?
It looks tasty.
Ouch.
Key.
Let me see. How is the wound?
It’s okay.
Let me take a look.
It’s really okay.
Key.
It hurts.
Let me see.
Where is it?
My heart hurts.
You hit me right in the heart.
It’s not funny, Key.
Chan, I’m just kidding.
Chan.
Please don’t be mad at me.
I’m not good at making up.
Chan, don’t be mad at me.
Please, please, please.
Didn’t you say
you’re not good at making up?
Yes.
I’m not good at making up.
But I’m good at something else.
Who taught you these lines?
I just can’t help it.
Shall we start?
Do you want to try the salmon?
Come on.
Aaah.
What will you have next?
This or this?
This.
Fine.
How is my skill?
Good.
I’m talking about my skill
from last night.
You, little perv.
Do you like it?
I’m talking about the food.
Do you want another bite?
I’ll help you put it on.
You smell good.
I can do it myself.
Yes, you can.
But it’s easier if I help.
I’m always your girl.
I want to be by your side
and take care of you for a long time.
It’s a business deal between us.
As long as our deal
has not been cancelled,
you can keep doing your job.
What if…
it’s not just a job?
If…
I really fall for you,
what will you do?
♪ Your only one ♪
♪ I’ll make you love me,
make you remember ♪
♪ I’ll keep repeating till you surrender ♪
♪ With every touch, remember only me ♪
♪ I’ll hold you close in everything I do ♪
♪ Make it sink in, make you remember too ♪
I heard that you went to my restaurant.
How was the food?
Was it good?
I can’t tell.
I ate only a little of it and left.
Why?
Didn’t Jay tell you why?
Phu.
Did Jay tell you to coax me again?
Jay asked me to talk to you
to persuade you to talk to her.
She wants to explain
why she broke up with you.
Don’t you want to know
why Jay suddenly left you and got married?
No.
Whatever her reason was,
it didn’t hold water.
What is the point of knowing it?
I know.
Jay did a terrible thing to you.
I also disappointed you.
I’m saying this as your friend.
I saw you’ve been hurt by this
for so long.
Chan.
Why don’t you hear her out?
Not to forgive her.
But for you to have your closure.
You can tell Jay
that I don’t want to hear it.
You should leave.
I have work to do.
This is Chan and Key.
Key.
Jay.
You can’t barge into my room.
This is too much.
You refuse to meet me.
So I have to do this.
You need to hear me today.
Just say what you want to say.
Do you remember Aunt Mon?
My aunt who raised me
after my parents died.
The truth is…
I’ve never had freedom in my life.
(Jay, you know that
I’m having a problem right now, right?)
Is it about money?
My investment didn’t go
as well as I thought.
Can you help me?
I need money to put into the investment.
Sure.
I have some savings.
I can give you 1 – 2 million baht.
Jay.
I need 10 million.
10 million?
Then you need to sell this house.
This house has been passed down
from your great-grandfather.
It belongs to our family.
How could I sell it?
Then how will you find 10 million baht?
Can you borrow it from Chan?
You want me to borrow money
from my girlfriend to give it to you?
Why not?
Your girlfriend is the firstborn heir
of the Pattarasemsawats.
Someone at her level
has the money to lend us.
I will never borrow money from Chan.
Why, Jay?
I told you.
Every relationship is transactional.
It’s not embarrassing to admit it.
But that’s not my relationship with Chan.
It’s not true, Jay.
When you are in a relationship,
you want love and desire from each other.
You need to be able to depend on
and help each other.
It provides mutual benefits
for both parties.
Hey.
Do you think
why I let you date her for this long?
You have many rich men pursuing you.
Do you think what my reason is?
You also said that last month.
How long do I have to wait?
We’re talking about millions,
not just a couple bucks.
If you can’t pay us back,
you should get ready
to spend time in jail.
I’ll find an investment fraud charge
against you.
So people will know that the Homwarangkul,
an old aristocratic family,
is actually a scammer.
Aunt.
Jay.
What should I do?
I didn’t mean it to end up like this.
It’s okay, Aunt.
We will work it out.
Work it out?
How, Jay?
The only solution to help me,
you refuse to do it.
If you agree to marry Derek,
the problem will be solved.
He is so crazy in love with you.
He has everything
and is willing to help us.
But I don’t love him.
Then tell the person you love to help me.
I’m your aunt.
Aren’t you going to help me
when I have a problem?
But this has nothing to do with Chan.
These debts are not mine.
What about the money that you spent?
The money that I used
to support you through school.
Where do you think it came from?
Huh?
Don’t be selfish, Jay.
Who do you think got you
where you are today?
Think about it.
If I lived alone,
I wouldn’t need this much money.
Why do I need to make a lot of money?
Because I need it to raise you.
Is this what you’ve thought all along?
Yes.
Without me,
do you think you can get this far, Jay?
Fine.
I…
I’ll marry Derek.
This is the last time
that I will help you.
From now on,
I will live my own life.
You should have done this sooner.
♪ No matter how hard I use my head,
I can’t fight it ♪
♪ I wanna erase you, but I can’t do it ♪
I’m sorry.
♪ In the end, my heart took over,
telling me this love is real ♪
♪ My whole heart still keeps on
missing you like this ♪
♪ You’re like a love song
that I can’t forget ♪
(After I married my husband,)
(he gave everything
my aunt had hoped for.)
(Her money problem was solved.)
(I got money to start my own business.)
When I completed my duty,
I divorced him.
I came back to you.
I never thought
that you were this kind of person.
So I could put an end to all of this.
Now, I’m free.
I can love you
without worrying about anything.
Don’t you think you are being too brazen?
I know.
I’m so shameless to come back to you.
But I came back
because I know
that you’re the one who truly loves me.
You bought me a ring.
You wanted to marry me.
Can you give me another chance?
Please let me make up
for the wrongs I’ve done to you.
No matter what your reason was.
From the day that you left me,
I stopped believing in love.
Chan.
I’m sorry.
I’m doing this.
It’s not because I can’t forgive you.
But our relationship is over.
It was all in the past. Do you get it?
Because of that girl, isn’t it?
It has nothing to do with Key.
Then why?
It’s because I have no love to give you.
No.
I told you.
The first kiss is like
smoking a cigarette.
You get excited only the first time.
But when we start to smoke again
after quitting it for a while,
we still feel that same excitement.
I think kissing works the same way.
Why don’t you kiss me?
So we’ll see if what I said was right.
If you kiss me
and you don’t feel that excitement,
I will let you go.
Key.
-Key.
-Chan.
What is the answer?
I don’t have feelings for you anymore.
Your kiss,
it means nothing to me.
It’s not true.
Jay.
I’m sorry.
No.
Goodbye, Jay.
No, this is not true.
Key.
Key, wait.
Please hear me out.
My heart,
it is beating fast only for you.
Every time I kiss you.
Whether it’s the first time
or any time after that,
my heart is always beating fast.
It happens only with you.
I love you.
♪ You don’t love me
for just one day, right? ♪
♪ Will you stay with me
through days and nights? ♪
♪ Each morning,
will I see your face next to mine? ♪
♪ You’re not just making my heart waver ♪
♪ Then leave me forever, no ♪
♪ A promise is a promise ♪
♪ Not just empty words, not a lie ♪
♪ This love is real ♪
♪ You don’t love me
for just one day, right? ♪
♪ Will you stay with me
through days and nights? ♪
♪ Each morning,
will I see your face next to mine? ♪
♪ You’re not just making my heart waver ♪
♪ Then leave me forever, no ♪
I want to cancel our deal.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Did you get the Treble Clef tattoo for me?
So I will remember you.
Tonight, I’m the only one
who can initiate kisses.
You can’t kiss me without my permission.
It’s obvious that Jay tries to do
everything to get my attention.
For the sake of our friendship,
I want you to go and talk to Jay.
Even if I can move on from Chan,
you and I can never be friends.
Your relationship with Chan
will not be easy.
Be careful.